<content>

Rule #1 'Common Sense'
Common sense is the ability to think and behave in a reasonable way and to make good decisions such as being naturally kind to innocent citizens, not spamming local ooc, refreainin from insulting others, and so on.

Rule #2 - 'Metagaming' 
Metagaming is simply defined as using out of character knowledge (such as communicating via teamspeak, private messages, and so on) for in character purposes.

A common example of metagaming would be reading someone's nametag to find out their character's name.

Punishments will vary depending on the sevirity and how did the metagaming affect the roleplay scenario.

Rule #3 - 'Powergaming'
Powergaming is forcing actions upon another player without giving them a chance to react, resist or fight back.
In addition, roleplaying a specific action with a very vague line is inappropriate and disallowed. Example: /me pats Samuel head to toe. 
In any case where you wish to hide an item on your body, say that an item is hidden somewhere, or rolpelay a very specific status of an item, the roleplay needs to be done clearly, and screenshotted for future reference. Also, driving with an inappropriate vehicle on inappropriate terrain, and attacking a player with a specific weapon via /me whilst you do not possess the said weapon is considered PG.


Rule #4 - 'Abusing Bugs'
 "The act of making use of a glitch to gain unfair advantage over another player" Exploiting bugs is definitely against the rules. Bugs and glitches are found quite regularly within MTA:SA and RP servers in general. If you encounter a bug or a glitch you must report it to the scripting team or to the staff team in general.

Rule #5 - 'Server Lore'
Bone County Roleplay has a server lore that makes individuals roleplay in a certain way. Check our forums for the Server Lore. This is how we're going to precisely roleplay in our server. Every individual playing Bone County Roleplay must abide to the said server lore.

Rule #6 - 'Begging' 
"The act of asking someone countless times for ooc possessions in-game" Asking for Game Coins (GCs), a higher rank in a faction via ooc chat is not allowed if done countless times ando with the intention of annoying someone. Use the /report system if you need something in particular or access the Requests section in the forums.

Rule #7 - 'IC & OOC' 
Everyone regardless of what they're doing are in-character. No one can go out-of-character without the permission of someone from the staff team unless they are being DMed or someone is unrealistically interfering with their roleplay.

Rule #8 - 'Robbing and Scamming'
Bone County Roleplay is an environment of realism, and with that being said, any items that you carry (weapons, money, valuable items, drugs, etc...) can be stolen from you any time. When a property is stolen, the robber must either keep its key or have access to the interior but must not be sold the property. When properties are to be broken into (accessed illegal, this does not mean the door has to be locked. If you're entering the interior that you do not own) you must report for an administrator, and the home owner must be online. Vehicles may be hotwired if the circumstances allow it. /report to have an admin assist and supervise you.

Rule #9 - 'Stealing Faction Vehicles'
Players are allowed to steal a faction vehicle as long as they provide a very detailed roleplay to the staff team. Not only that but the individual must have a valid reason to perform te act. Additionally, they must report for an administrator to supervise the situation. Keep in mind that most government vehicles are equipped with hidden GPS trackers.

      

This is our server. We want everyone to have lots of fun playing on it together. If you see someone breaking one of the rules above, don't hesitate in /report or hitting F2.
We'd like to thank you for taking time to read all of this.
</content>
